https://onfrozenblog.wordpress.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
We highly value your privacy and make this policy easily available to assist you in understanding the handling of information in the course of using this site, On Frozen Blog (OFB).
Log Files and Cookies
OFB utilizes industry standard analytics packages which gathers limited information on visitors to our website automatically, and stores this anonymous information in server log files. This information may include IP addresses, browser type, basic IP information, referring pages, operating system used and date/time stamps. This information does not identify individual users; it is used only for site administration, as well as for analysis of website usage and trends.
Additionally, cookies may be used to provide easier and faster access to website features such as logins and/or repeat visits. Cookies are very small text files that are stored on personal computers for reference purposes. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally indentifiable information you have submitted while on our site.
We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. A session cookie expires when your browser is closed, and a persistent cookie may stay on your hard drive for an extended period. Session cookies make it easier for you to navigate our site; persistent cookies can perform such activities as storing your password for forums or blogs so you do not have to sign in every time you visit those areas, and/or may be used to enable us to track and target the interests of our users so as to enhance the overall experience of using our site.
We have no access to or administration abilities over any cookies that are used by any advertisers on our site.
Links to Other Websites
OFB contains links to other sites that are not controlled in any way by us. Please be aware of this when you click on any such links; we are not responsible for the privacy practices and/or policies of any website other than our own. Consequently, we strongly suggest that you review the privacy policy of every website you visit, whether or not they are linked to by our own site.
Registration and Use of Personal Information
Registration is not required in order to use or access OFB. However, you may be required to register for forums, message boards, email subscriptions or other similar features, particularly if you wish to leave comments.
If you do register, and in the process provide us with personally identifiable information, rest assured that any such information you provide will not be shared with any third-party organization except with your express consent.
Please note that if you post comments or articles to any forum, blog or message board on OFB, any personally identifiable information you provide in those comments or articles may be read, collated and used by anyone viewing them. As such, we are not responsible for personally identifiable information you may choose to make available through these channels. (Email addresses required when commenting are NOT publicly shown on the web site.)
We also provide visitors to our website the opportunity to opt-in to receive communications from us. In this case, we ask the visitor for his or her email address. These communications may include our regular newsletter, product promotions and any other information that we feel may be pertinent to the visitor. You may opt out of receiving these communications by clicking on the ‘unsubscribe’ link in any email we send to you.
Again, if you provide us with your email address and/or name for the purposes of receiving communications from us, this information will not be shared with any third-party organization except with your express consent.
Access to Personally Identifiable Information
If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer wish us to possess your information, you may request correction, updating, or deletion of your information by emailing us at [provide working email address].[if applicable] You may also complete any corrections, updates or deletion requests at [provide URL]; you also may make your request by phone or postal mail at the address/phone number indicated at the end of this privacy policy.
Security
We follow accepted industry standards to protect any personal information you have provided to us. However, please be aware that no method of electronic storage can ever be 100% secure. Therefore — as is the case with any organization – we are not in a position to guarantee the absolute security of your information.
Legal Disclaimer
We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order or legal process served on our website.
Contact Details
If you have any questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy, or you wish to contact us, our contact information is as follows:
Email OFB
This privacy policy was last updated on 23 October, 2009.
Share this:TwitterFacebookLike this:Like Loading...
Search for:
Blog at WordPress.com.
Privacy & Cookies: This site uses cookies. By continuing to use this website, you agree to their use.
To find out more, including how to control cookies, see here:
Cookie Policy
%d bloggers like this:
